<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
  <statement id="1">Online communities can provide quick and practical advice.</statement>
  <statement id="2">I avoid asking teachers for help because I don’t want to appear incompetent.</statement>
  <statement id="3">Friends in China comfort me emotionally, but their advice does not always fit my situation in the UK.</statement>
  <statement id="4">Staff in my accommodation (e.g., the front desk) can be helpful with practical issues.</statement>
  <statement id="5">I hesitate to use university services because I am not sure which office to contact.</statement>
  <statement id="6">It is often hard to judge whether online information is reliable.</statement>
  <statement id="7">My roommates have helped me deal with everyday problems in the UK.</statement>
  <statement id="8">Local British students often do not fully understand the challenges I face.</statement>
  <statement id="9">The cost of counselling discourages me from using it.</statement>
  <statement id="10">People in my course (e.g., group members) have helped me when I needed support.</statement>
  <statement id="11">Chinese friends often provide practical information about living in the UK.</statement>
  <statement id="12">Talking with my parents makes me feel emotionally supported.</statement>
  <statement id="13">I worry about being judged when asking local British students for help.</statement>
  <statement id="14">Community or student organizations provide social connection more than practical support.</statement>
  <statement id="15">I do not fully trust the university’s mental health services.</statement>
  <statement id="16">Neighbors can help with small practical matters in daily life.</statement>
  <statement id="17">Spending time with Chinese classmates gives me a sense of belonging.</statement>
  <statement id="18">When I ask course tutors or lecturers for help, I usually get a useful response.</statement>
  <statement id="19">My academic supervisor has provided me with important guidance.</statement>
  <statement id="20">I find counselling helpful when my stress becomes hard to manage.</statement>
  <statement id="21">I would rather solve problems by myself than contact university student office.</statement>
  <statement id="22">My parents’ involvement in my personal life sometimes increases my pressure.</statement>
  <statement id="23">Online groups can help me feel less lonely.</statement>
  <statement id="24">I avoid telling my family about my problems because I don’t want them to worry.</statement>
  <statement id="25">Complicated procedures in the healthcare system can be frustrating.</statement>
  <statement id="26">I am willing to seek help from local British friends to learn about the culture.</statement>
  <statement id="27">The university’s international office has helped me solve practical problems.</statement>
  <statement id="28">People I am not close to (e.g., acquaintances or service staff) can still provide practical help in daily life.</statement>
  <statement id="29">It is difficult for me to build close friendships with local British students.</statement>
  <statement id="30">When I feel overwhelmed, I often turn to Chinese friends first.</statement>
  <statement id="31">University support often focuses more on academics than on daily-life needs.</statement>
  <statement id="32">Financial support from my parents makes me feel secure while studying in the UK.</statement>
  <statement id="33">I sometimes feel pressured to keep up appearances within Chinese circles.</statement>
  <statement id="34">Supervisors can also offer valuable advice on non-academic matters.</statement>
  <statement id="35">I feel uncomfortable discussing personal issues with professionals I don’t know.</statement>
  <statement id="36">Friendships with other international students help me adapt to a multicultural environment.</statement>
  <statement id="37">I feel more comfortable asking other international students for advice than asking local British students.</statement>
  <statement id="38">I often get information about living in the UK from platforms like Xiaohongshu or Weibo.</statement>
  <statement id="39">My roommates have offered emotional comfort when I felt stressed.</statement>
  <statement id="40">I sometimes worry that joining student associations may affect how others see me.</statement>
</statements>
